Rayhan Shidqi



Personal Information

Project Portfolio: rayhanshidqi.com

Email:

rayhanshidqi.j@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/rayhanshidqi

GitHub:

github.com/eaqyyy

Education

BINUS University

Bachelor of Computer Science 2017 – February 2021 (expected) GPA 3.5 / 4.0

Summary

Rayhan is a final year computer science student that is expected to graduate in February 2021. He will be graduating from university within 3.5 years with 1 year worth of internship experience. He is well-versed in many programming languages and specialized in full-stack development. To hone his teamwork and public speaking skills, Rayhan also has won a few international debating tournaments.

Technical Skills

Programming

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Python
- Java
- C/C++

Framework & Database

- React
- Angular
- Express
- Django
- NoSQL & SQL

Experience

Full-stack Developer Intern — February 2020 to February 2021 Jenius (Bank BTPN), Jakarta

- Developed an applicant tracking software to ease and speed-up recruitment process of IT talent.
- Developed a server notification software that automatically deliver report analysis & critical server alerts.
- Stack used: React/Angular, Express, and MongoDB.
- The code are written in a clean and testable manner.

Technical Support Intern – January 2016 to March 2021 **LKBN Antara, High School Summer Break Internship**, Jakarta

- Designed networking route for different office floors.
- Virtualized server with Microsoft HyperV.

Academic Achievements

- Recepient of Outstanding Students Scholarship, 2019
- Australasians Intervarsity Debating Championship, 2019 EFL Champion. The biggest intercontinental debating tournament ever held. Topics of discussion includes technology, economy, politics, and environment.
- United Asians Debating Championship, 2019 –
 EFL Champion & Top 10 Best EFL Speaker Nominee.
 A highly-celebrated debating tournament that welcomes prestigious universities across Asia.
- Asian English Olympics, 2020 –
 Debating Champion & 4th Best Speaker. Matched against students from multiple countries in Asia; China, Hong Kong, Taiwan, Bangladesh, and Vietnam.